{
    "id": "5a4393113766439d8e66055faa1eff01",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There are four stages …………….. the metamorphosis of a mosquito.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t find anything ……………………. this messy desk.",
            "description": "On indicates position on the surface of something.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Trying to define God led us ………………….. even more metaphysical questions.",
            "description": "Led is used with to.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was praised ……………………… his meritorious service.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The caretaker showed no mercy ……………………. trespassers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Dickens was a great writer ……………………….. his tearful plots.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction despite is used alone without of.",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "despite of",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The car was going ………………………. its maximum speed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the two examples, I prefer the latter.",
            "description": "Of is the correct word here.",
            "answers": [
                "From",
                "Of",
                "In"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The clown made the children laugh ………………………… joy.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which say how people are showing their emotions. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The comedian finally got a laugh ………………………… the unresponsive audience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You will be a laughingstock …………………….. that silly outfit.",
            "description": "We use in to say what people are wearing. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I had her knack ……………………… cooking.",
            "description": "Knack is used with for.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}